A Guide to the Social Science Research Council records, Administration and Officers Files, Presidents' Office FA1827
Rockefeller Archive Center
- Committee Overview Files, 1990-1995; 6; 2.66 Cubic Feet 7 letter document boxes
  - Urban Underclass - Hispanic Committee Coordination, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 609)
  - Urban Underclass - Bob Pearson Replacement Search, 1990 (Box 54, Folder 619)
    Restricted - Executive Search - Open in 2030
  - Urban Underclass Policy Advisory Group, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 610)
  - Urban Underclass - Rockefeller Foundation Evaluation, 1990 (Box 53, Folder 611)
  - International Predissertation Fellowship Program (IPFP), 1990-1994 (Box 53, Folder 612)
  - International and Peace and Security, 1990-1995 (Box 53, Folder 613)
  - Western Europe, 1990-1994 (Box 53, Folder 614)
  - Near and Middle East, 1991-1994 (Box 54, Folder 615)
  - Soviet Studies, 1992 (Box 54, Folder 616)
  - Southeast Asia, 1991-1995 (Box 54, Folder 617)